TOHO
Today's so lively!
They have left the burnt fireworks just like this! How terrible!
Catch the ball, Nobita!
What?! Where?!
Look above your head!
We've won!
Nobita, why didn't you catch the ball?
Ouch! Where is GIant?
Look above!
Cheer up, Nobita-san!
Bye!
Now I remember!
Ah, that's my teddy bear!
Hey!
Memories
of
Grandma
I knew it!
Nobita!
Welcome home!
Mum, why did you throw away my little teddy?
"My little teddy" he says...
Why now? You ignored it all this time!
You should just discard it!
Come on!
My little teddy is no trash!
What's up with him today?
That's it!
Here's the bandage, Nobita-kun!
Thanks!
That's it!
That stuffed teddy means so much to you?
Yup.
I finished bandaging my teddy!
Shall I heal it with the Time Cloth?
No way!
But it's all dirty and worn out!
It's fine!
Look!
But look at all those patches.
Yeah, my grandma always fixed the teddy for me.
You have a grandma?
She passed away when I was in the kindergarten, though.
Now I remember!
I have her photos.
Nobita-chan's Memories
This is her.
She's holding you.
She looks kind.
Sure, she is. She loved me a lot.
She always enveloped me with love, warmth and stood by me always.
I'd love to see her alive once again!
Then I can have my little teddy fixed.
That's it!
We can just use the Time Machine to see her alive once again!
Wait! That's not a good idea!
But why?
When she sees you all grown up, what's she going to think?
She'd probably flipped over in shock!
Uh... We can just explain the situation?
You think she'll understand the Time Machine?
But... Still...
Memories are meant to be buried in the depths of one's heart.
Then let's just have a peek at her!
Let's hide somewhere and have a peek at her!
It should be fine as long as we don't meet or reach out to her.
You promise to?
Yes, just a peek, promise!
Fine!
Yay! Let's board!
Hop in!
Coming!
Nobita!!
I wonder where did he went....
He left it damaged! For god's sake!
Let's go back to the time when I was 3.
Sure thing!
We're here!
Huh?
This is our playbase!
Yup.
But why didn't we jump in to our house?
If anyone sees us, there'd be panic!
Now I see!
We're going!
It looked so spacious!
That's because you were still very tiny...
Let's shift to the gardens.
Wow, this place hasn't changed a bit!
This is our garden!
It's the sandbox!
Someone will find us! Let's quickly take a peek of grandma.
Let's enter from the backdoor.
Pass-Through Hoop!
Hello!
Excuse us!
That tea plate!
Enough, we're going back!
Sorry...
Grandma always stayed in that room!
Listen, we're just going to take a peek at her!
Huh, she's not here!
Oh, my?
Maybe she's watching TV!
Quietly!
She's not here neither!
She must be in the living room then.
Not here neither!
Maybe she's upstairs!
The door won't open! This door was always like that!
If pulling doens't work, push it! Heave ho!
Who are you kids and what are you doing in our house?!
Oh, my! You're so young!
Oh, really?
But your face will be covered with wrinkles very soon.
Oh, my, I'll be like a white Manjuu and....
Who are you two, sneaking into peoples' homes?
Maybe she didn't recognize us?!
Of course not!
Let's look for grandma, come on!
That's...
That's me, at age 3...
How cute!
Nothing like you are now...
It's Giant and Suneo! I'll make you two pay!
Nobita-kun!
How dare you bully me!
They're just kids!
But at today's baseball match, they....
Don't mix up the past and the present!
Sorry, kids!
How cute!
How and what part of it?
You alirght, Nobi-chan?
It's Shizuka-chan!
Don't cry. I'll walk you to your house.
Oh you, your face is all red!
Nevermind, let's see Grandma!
She wasn't at our home road.
She's probably at the bookstore.
Let's go to the bookstore and see if she's there!
It's Grandma!
She's alive!
So nostalgic!
Welcome home, grandma!
I'm home!
Did you get dumplings for me?
Sorry, but your favorite dumplings sold out.
In place, I've brought your favorite Ohagi.
Don't wanna! I want dumplings!
Sorry!
i hate you grandma! Go away!
Grandma, get lost!
Nobita-kun!
Hey, you! Don't yell at grandma!
Why do you pick on my Nobita?!
I can explain the very deep meaning behind my actions, actually I'm Nobita!
But Nobita is my boy here!
Actually, I'm Nobita from the future.
I time traveled via the Time Machine...
This boy must be mad!
Mum!
Stop!
Grandma, when I grow up, I will open a toy shop.
Oh, really?
I'm gonna play with my toys and teddy.
Is that so?
What do you want me to become, grandma?
I wonder...
I hate you, grandma!
Go away!
Let's go home, Nobita-kun!
But I was very mean to my grandma.
You're just a preschooler, so that doesn't matter.
I love my grandma.
Now listen, you're in the past to see your grandma
Although you were selfish... your grandma loves you.
It's your grandma!
That teddy bear!
They went to the toy shop.
She's buying you a new toy. Now let's head back home.
But they didn't buy anything, it seems.
Nevermind that.
They didn't buy any toy here neither.
Aren't they just gazing at the toys?
No, they must be looking for something!
And what might that be?
I don't remember clearly, but I have remember something.
They didn't find what they were looking for.
They're still at it. She might faint!
I wonder if she can go on....
There, you must be tired!
He's asleep.
I wonder what they were looking for.
You're awake, now?
Grandma, did you buy me fireworks?
Fireworks!
Tell me, grandma!
Sorry, Nobi-chan. But they only sell fireworks in the summer.
We searched all over and didn't find it.
NO!
Fireworks!
Go away, grandma!
Sure, sure...
I hate you, grandma!
Oh no! She's coming this way!
She almost found us!
It's fall and he wants fireworks...
I'm very selfish!
Don't come any closer! No!
Ah, Nobi-chan!
Stop!
It's nice to see you all here...
Gimme back my teddy!
Oh, why?
Doraemon, what happened?!
I'm stuck!
That's the boy from then, and that's Nobita's precious teddy.
Gimme that!
I can explain the circumstances!
Watch out!
-Stop!
Gimme Nobita's teddy!
Gimme that!
Giant! Suneo!
I'm sorry, please forgive us!
Got off!
Stop!
Run!
Don't!
We won! Let's give back the teddy to Nobita!
You can only deliberately lose so many times.
I wonder where grandma is.
Nobita-kun, we saw her, isn't that enough?
Let's head back!
I wanna see grandma just one more time, please?!
Nobita-kun!
Mum, I must pee!
Mum, it's the weirdo from the earlier.
Mum!
Are you sure?
Yup.
Mother-in-law, did any strange boy come here?
Nah.
I see. Maybe I should file a complaint with the police.
Thank you for hiding me.
Are you leaving already?
You won't suspect me, grandma?
No.
Bye!
Boy, you brought back this teddy, right?
Sure, I did.
Thanks really.
Now for the stitching...
I guess I'll use this cloth.
See?
Yeah.
Grandma, do you find your Nobita-kun, adorable?
Why, of course I do.
I want to stand by him always and take a good care of him, but...
But I can't.
I'm already aged, so...
Please don't say such sad things...
Wish I could be alive till when he's a first grader.
I'd love to see him wearing his uniform and his randsel bag.
I'll be back.
Oh, it's my schoolbag.
Doraemon!
Come here quickly!
Thanks, Doraemon.
But only this time.
Grandma.
Grandma, while it may be hard to believe me, but I'm actually Nobita.
Nobita, the 4th-grader.
So you really are.
I knew it must be you.
Do you really believe me?
Who'd suspect you?
Grandma!
I missed you so much, grandma!
I know.
Sorry for being very selfish, grandma.
I'm the one who's at fault.
I just wanted to see you happy!
But I couldn't make you happy.
That's why you tell me to go away!
I'm very happy to see your smiling face.
I'm glad I'm your grandmother.
"I'm glad I'm your grandmother"
Grandma!
Thanks, Nobi-chan!
What do you want me to be when I grow up?
I already saw you all grown-up, so....
What did I become? Tell me!
My grandson.
Huh? The ears are fully stitched.
The arms too!
True!
But who could've?...
It's bath-time!
Mum did it...
Mum!
Thanks for stitching my little teddy.
You're very welcome.
Why are you wearing your school bag?
Well...
The important thing is simply maintaining your silence!
That was over 100 years ago
But even if I put it into words, I'm sure that's all there is to it
I really don't have anything
If you say you love me, give me a hug
I feel good, so please hug me again.
Because I'm always lonely
I want to feel the warmth together
Don't be embarrassed, be brave
Come on, let's all hug together
I'm not alone, I'm not scared
I'LL GIVE YOU A HUG to you too
Let's hug!